var questions =[{
    question: 'Commonly known as the "Barkless Dog", this small breed from Africa has a distinctive "yodel" that it uses to comunicate.',
	 answers: ['Beagle'
	 ,'Sloughi'
	 ,'Basenji'
     ,'Maltese'],
     correctAnswer : 2
},
{
    question :'This arctic working dog is one of the most common breeds to be crossed with a wolf.',
	answers:[' Siberian Husky'
	,' Bernese Mountain Dog'
	,' Lhasa Apso'
    ,' Samoyed'],
    correctAnswer: 0
},
{
    question :'These water retrievers are popular parents for many different "designer" dogs.',
	answers:[' German Shephard'
	,' Portugese Water Dog'
    ,' Boxer'
    ,' Standard Poodle'],
    correctAnswer: 3
},
{
    question :'This distinctive-looking dog was bred to guard horses and coaches, and now rides in big red trucks.',
	answers:[' Great Dane'
	,' Dalmation'
    ,' German Shepherd'
    ,' Cocker Spaniel'],
    correctAnswer: 1
},
{
    question :'This small, Japanese hunting breed is often called "catlike" for its tendency to bond strongly to a single person and ignore everyone else.',
	answers:[' Shiba Inu'
	,' Beagle'
    ,' Pointer'
    ,' Akita'],
    correctAnswer: 0
},
{
    question :'These hunting breeds get their name from the ability to freeze in place and look straight at its prey to tell the hunter where it is hiding.',
	answers:[' Beagles'
	,' Setters'
    ,' Shepherds'
    ,' Pointers'],
    correctAnswer: 3
},
{
    question :'Huskies are not the only dogs bred to move loads. These drafting dogs were bred to pull carts of hay around the farm.',
	answers:[' Burnese Mountain Dog'
	,' Giant Schnauzer'
    ,' Leonburger'
    ,' Mastiff'],
    correctAnswer: 0
},
{
    question :'This diminuituve breed comes in two varieties, the striking "Hairless" and the cuddly "powderpuff".',
	answers:[' Havanese'
	,' Chinese Crested'
    ,' Yorkshire Terrier'
    ,' Maltese'],
    correctAnswer: 1
},
{
    question :'This beloved breed came to America from England where it was used as a fighting/baiting dog, and is a common ancestor to many of today\'s "bully" and "pit" breeds.',
	answers:[' Staffordshore Terrier'
	,' Bulldog'
    ,' Pit Bull'
    ,' Bull Terrier'],
    correctAnswer: 1
},
{
    question :'This comically short dog is an expert at herding and a favorite of English royalty.',
	answers:[' Border Collie'
	,' Anatolian Shepherd Dog'
    ,' Australian Sheepdog'
    ,' Corgi'],
    correctAnswer: 3
}]

